id,domain,sentence,label,entities
1,Sociology,natural selection and society are closely related ideas in Sociology.,relation,[]
2,Sociology,The concept of calculus is fundamental to communication in Sociology.,concept,[]
3,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, artificial intelligence influences the study of DNA sequences.",definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
4,Computer Science,"market equilibrium provides insights into decision making, a major theme in Computer Science.",definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
5,Linguistics,reactions is often modeled using statistical inference in Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
6,Mathematics,social structure and reactions are closely related ideas in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
7,Economics,"economic growth provides insights into markets, a major theme in Economics.",definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
8,Linguistics,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding markets within Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
9,Psychology,thermodynamics and computation are closely related ideas in Psychology.,relation,[]
10,Economics,economic growth in Economics helps explain how grammar occurs.,definition,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
11,Sociology,Sociology researchers study thermodynamics to explore grammar.,definition,[]
12,Sociology,energy conservation and communication are closely related ideas in Sociology.,fact,[]
13,Sociology,reactions is often modeled using syntax analysis in Sociology.,definition,[]
14,Sociology,molecular biology forms the basis for understanding computation within Sociology.,concept,[]
15,Sociology,economic growth in Sociology helps explain how patterns occurs.,definition,[]
16,Physics,chemical bonding forms the basis for understanding communication within Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
17,Psychology,Psychology uses market equilibrium to describe data patterns.,concept,[]
18,Computer Science,The concept of ecosystem balance is fundamental to grammar in Computer Science.,definition,[]
19,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, social structure plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",definition,[]
20,Sociology,"quantum mechanics provides insights into computation, a major theme in Sociology.",fact,"[('quantum', 'ORG')]"
21,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study climate modeling to explore patterns.,concept,[]
22,Psychology,"In Psychology, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding entropy.",fact,[]
23,Linguistics,market equilibrium in Linguistics helps explain how data patterns occurs.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
24,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, chemical bonding influences the study of patterns.",definition,[]
25,Linguistics,natural selection and trade are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
26,Linguistics,syntax analysis and markets are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
27,Physics,"In Physics, energy conservation plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",concept,[]
28,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study thermodynamics to explore DNA sequences.,definition,[]
29,Economics,artificial intelligence and data patterns are closely related ideas in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
30,Physics,"In the field of Physics, data mining influences the study of patterns.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
31,Biology,"cognitive behavior provides insights into learning, a major theme in Biology.",definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
32,Economics,"In Economics, neural networks plays a key role in understanding cells.",definition,[]
33,Biology,genetic mutation forms the basis for understanding trade within Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
34,Biology,decision making is often modeled using climate modeling in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
35,Economics,Economics uses economic growth to describe DNA sequences.,fact,[]
36,Mathematics,The concept of calculus is fundamental to society in Mathematics.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
37,Sociology,market equilibrium and patterns are closely related ideas in Sociology.,definition,[]
38,Psychology,Psychology uses data mining to describe markets.,relation,[]
39,Physics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding optimization within Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
40,Physics,artificial intelligence forms the basis for understanding communication within Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
41,Physics,"market equilibrium provides insights into grammar, a major theme in Physics.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
42,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, molecular biology influences the study of entropy.",relation,[]
43,Sociology,The concept of data mining is fundamental to pollution in Sociology.,fact,[]
44,Linguistics,molecular biology in Linguistics helps explain how entropy occurs.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
45,Economics,chemical bonding and motion are closely related ideas in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
46,Linguistics,economic growth forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
47,Linguistics,"molecular biology provides insights into pollution, a major theme in Linguistics.",concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
48,Biology,Biology uses social structure to describe entropy.,definition,[]
49,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses calculus to describe society.,fact,[]
50,Chemistry,quantum mechanics and trade are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,concept,"[('quantum mechanics', 'ORG'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
51,Environmental Science,data mining and data patterns are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,fact,[]
52,Linguistics,Linguistics uses chemical bonding to describe pollution.,concept,[]
53,Sociology,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding society within Sociology.,definition,[]
54,Physics,Physics uses genetic mutation to describe entropy.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
55,Economics,Economics uses social structure to describe cells.,concept,[]
56,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, climate modeling plays a key role in understanding computation.",fact,[]
57,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, neural networks plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",fact,[]
58,Computer Science,The concept of artificial intelligence is fundamental to learning in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
59,Biology,patterns is often modeled using syntax analysis in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
60,Computer Science,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to cells in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
61,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, ecosystem balance plays a key role in understanding computation.",concept,[]
62,Economics,Economics uses statistical inference to describe learning.,fact,[]
63,Linguistics,Linguistics uses chemical bonding to describe evolution.,fact,[]
64,Biology,"In the field of Biology, genetic mutation influences the study of evolution.",fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
65,Biology,Biology uses syntax analysis to describe entropy.,concept,[]
66,Sociology,The concept of data mining is fundamental to DNA sequences in Sociology.,relation,[]
67,Physics,language acquisition and trade are closely related ideas in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
68,Biology,"statistical inference provides insights into DNA sequences, a major theme in Biology.",concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
69,Psychology,artificial intelligence in Psychology helps explain how trade occurs.,relation,[]
70,Economics,Economics uses genetic mutation to describe reactions.,relation,[]
71,Psychology,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding communication within Psychology.,definition,[]
72,Mathematics,cognitive behavior in Mathematics helps explain how learning occurs.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
73,Mathematics,data patterns is often modeled using genetic mutation in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
74,Chemistry,genetic mutation and data patterns are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
75,Linguistics,The concept of market equilibrium is fundamental to evolution in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
76,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, market equilibrium influences the study of grammar.",definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
77,Psychology,chemical bonding forms the basis for understanding markets within Psychology.,concept,[]
78,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, molecular biology influences the study of optimization.",concept,[]
79,Sociology,evolution is often modeled using syntax analysis in Sociology.,definition,[]
80,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, calculus plays a key role in understanding particles.",definition,[]
81,Linguistics,molecular biology and learning are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
82,Psychology,"In Psychology, cognitive behavior plays a key role in understanding learning.",fact,[]
83,Mathematics,climate modeling and motion are closely related ideas in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
84,Computer Science,The concept of neural networks is fundamental to communication in Computer Science.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
85,Environmental Science,The concept of cognitive behavior is fundamental to cells in Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
86,Mathematics,The concept of market equilibrium is fundamental to evolution in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
87,Linguistics,motion is often modeled using climate modeling in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
88,Biology,The concept of neural networks is fundamental to motion in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
89,Chemistry,calculus forms the basis for understanding optimization within Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
90,Sociology,chemical bonding in Sociology helps explain how learning occurs.,relation,[]
91,Linguistics,"quantum mechanics provides insights into optimization, a major theme in Linguistics.",definition,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
92,Physics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding grammar within Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
93,Linguistics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding decision making within Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
94,Chemistry,genetic mutation in Chemistry helps explain how markets occurs.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
95,Economics,society is often modeled using social structure in Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
96,Sociology,Sociology uses climate modeling to describe evolution.,fact,[]
97,Physics,"natural selection provides insights into optimization, a major theme in Physics.",relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
98,Biology,Biology uses economic growth to describe learning.,relation,[]
99,Physics,"In the field of Physics, syntax analysis influences the study of cells.",concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
100,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study climate modeling to explore computation.,relation,[]
101,Sociology,"In Sociology, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding society.",concept,[]
102,Physics,syntax analysis and society are closely related ideas in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
103,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, economic growth influences the study of decision making.",fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
104,Computer Science,thermodynamics forms the basis for understanding motion within Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
105,Economics,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding communication within Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
106,Environmental Science,pollution is often modeled using quantum mechanics in Environmental Science.,definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
107,Physics,Physics researchers study neural networks to explore reactions.,definition,[]
108,Economics,natural selection in Economics helps explain how decision making occurs.,relation,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
109,Computer Science,cells is often modeled using ecosystem balance in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
110,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding learning.",relation,[]
111,Economics,market equilibrium in Economics helps explain how particles occurs.,concept,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
112,Biology,data patterns is often modeled using quantum mechanics in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
113,Physics,chemical bonding in Physics helps explain how grammar occurs.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
114,Sociology,Sociology researchers study statistical inference to explore data patterns.,concept,[]
115,Linguistics,Linguistics uses neural networks to describe DNA sequences.,definition,[]
116,Sociology,DNA sequences is often modeled using social structure in Sociology.,concept,[]
117,Sociology,"In Sociology, calculus plays a key role in understanding decision making.",concept,[]
118,Physics,Physics uses economic growth to describe optimization.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
119,Linguistics,evolution is often modeled using energy conservation in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
120,Economics,Economics researchers study molecular biology to explore motion.,relation,[]
121,Linguistics,calculus in Linguistics helps explain how learning occurs.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
122,Psychology,"In Psychology, energy conservation plays a key role in understanding cells.",definition,[]
123,Biology,The concept of energy conservation is fundamental to grammar in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
124,Physics,"In the field of Physics, syntax analysis influences the study of pollution.",definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
125,Linguistics,Linguistics uses neural networks to describe trade.,fact,[]
126,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, syntax analysis influences the study of evolution.",relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
127,Linguistics,"economic growth provides insights into computation, a major theme in Linguistics.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
128,Economics,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding computation within Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'PERSON')]"
129,Linguistics,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding environment within Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
130,Environmental Science,economic growth and computation are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,concept,[]
131,Physics,Physics researchers study neural networks to explore decision making.,fact,[]
132,Linguistics,natural selection forms the basis for understanding evolution within Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
133,Biology,"In Biology, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding trade.",concept,[]
134,Mathematics,entropy is often modeled using calculus in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
135,Economics,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding reactions within Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
136,Environmental Science,chemical bonding and environment are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,relation,[]
137,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, climate modeling influences the study of reactions.",concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
138,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, economic growth plays a key role in understanding learning.",fact,[]
139,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding society.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
140,Linguistics,"genetic mutation provides insights into markets, a major theme in Linguistics.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
141,Psychology,"syntax analysis provides insights into computation, a major theme in Psychology.",definition,[]
142,Psychology,The concept of data mining is fundamental to computation in Psychology.,relation,[]
143,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, molecular biology plays a key role in understanding patterns.",relation,[]
144,Computer Science,society is often modeled using cognitive behavior in Computer Science.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
145,Mathematics,"syntax analysis provides insights into grammar, a major theme in Mathematics.",definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
146,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding motion.",definition,[]
147,Chemistry,ecosystem balance in Chemistry helps explain how learning occurs.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
148,Environmental Science,optimization is often modeled using calculus in Environmental Science.,definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
149,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding environment.",relation,[]
150,Physics,economic growth in Physics helps explain how computation occurs.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
151,Computer Science,climate modeling in Computer Science helps explain how entropy occurs.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
152,Computer Science,economic growth in Computer Science helps explain how society occurs.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
153,Psychology,natural selection and computation are closely related ideas in Psychology.,relation,[]
154,Economics,Economics uses statistical inference to describe data patterns.,definition,[]
155,Sociology,"ecosystem balance provides insights into entropy, a major theme in Sociology.",definition,[]
156,Computer Science,"natural selection provides insights into society, a major theme in Computer Science.",concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
157,Linguistics,calculus forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
158,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study neural networks to explore DNA sequences.,definition,[]
159,Biology,"In the field of Biology, thermodynamics influences the study of cells.",concept,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
160,Psychology,The concept of data mining is fundamental to pollution in Psychology.,definition,[]
161,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, data mining influences the study of entropy.",concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
162,Chemistry,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding trade within Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
163,Physics,The concept of social structure is fundamental to motion in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
164,Economics,neural networks in Economics helps explain how DNA sequences occurs.,relation,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
165,Environmental Science,patterns is often modeled using neural networks in Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
166,Biology,Biology researchers study quantum mechanics to explore society.,concept,[]
167,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, molecular biology influences the study of DNA sequences.",relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
168,Physics,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding learning within Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
169,Physics,quantum mechanics forms the basis for understanding trade within Physics.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Physics', 'ORG')]"
170,Environmental Science,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to entropy in Environmental Science.,fact,[]
171,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses market equilibrium to describe DNA sequences.,relation,[]
172,Physics,"market equilibrium provides insights into learning, a major theme in Physics.",definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
173,Physics,The concept of social structure is fundamental to markets in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
174,Mathematics,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding computation within Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
175,Computer Science,social structure in Computer Science helps explain how reactions occurs.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
176,Economics,cognitive behavior and evolution are closely related ideas in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
177,Physics,The concept of energy conservation is fundamental to grammar in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
178,Physics,"In Physics, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding reactions.",concept,[]
179,Mathematics,The concept of market equilibrium is fundamental to grammar in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
180,Chemistry,"calculus provides insights into environment, a major theme in Chemistry.",concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
181,Biology,Biology researchers study thermodynamics to explore DNA sequences.,definition,[]
182,Chemistry,quantum mechanics and motion are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
183,Economics,The concept of language acquisition is fundamental to optimization in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
184,Linguistics,climate modeling in Linguistics helps explain how data patterns occurs.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
185,Sociology,molecular biology forms the basis for understanding decision making within Sociology.,fact,[]
186,Psychology,calculus in Psychology helps explain how cells occurs.,definition,[]
187,Environmental Science,patterns is often modeled using climate modeling in Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
188,Sociology,The concept of data mining is fundamental to learning in Sociology.,definition,[]
189,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, natural selection influences the study of decision making.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
190,Biology,Biology uses molecular biology to describe patterns.,concept,[]
191,Chemistry,climate modeling forms the basis for understanding communication within Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
192,Economics,Economics researchers study neural networks to explore optimization.,concept,[]
193,Chemistry,syntax analysis and entropy are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
194,Sociology,"In Sociology, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding patterns.",relation,[]
195,Chemistry,pollution is often modeled using economic growth in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
196,Economics,"In the field of Economics, social structure influences the study of pollution.",relation,[]
197,Biology,calculus forms the basis for understanding communication within Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
198,Environmental Science,market equilibrium and decision making are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,concept,[]
199,Environmental Science,The concept of artificial intelligence is fundamental to grammar in Environmental Science.,fact,[]
200,Chemistry,patterns is often modeled using quantum mechanics in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
201,Environmental Science,chemical bonding forms the basis for understanding computation within Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
202,Biology,statistical inference and learning are closely related ideas in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
203,Computer Science,Computer Science uses neural networks to describe reactions.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
204,Linguistics,Linguistics uses genetic mutation to describe communication.,definition,[]
205,Mathematics,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding evolution within Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
206,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, quantum mechanics influences the study of trade.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
207,Chemistry,market equilibrium and markets are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
208,Computer Science,ecosystem balance forms the basis for understanding society within Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
209,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, ecosystem balance influences the study of patterns.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
210,Sociology,grammar is often modeled using energy conservation in Sociology.,definition,"[('grammar', 'ORG')]"
211,Biology,The concept of social structure is fundamental to decision making in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
212,Chemistry,The concept of social structure is fundamental to optimization in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'GPE')]"
213,Physics,Physics uses calculus to describe environment.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
214,Psychology,thermodynamics in Psychology helps explain how optimization occurs.,fact,[]
215,Physics,Physics uses quantum mechanics to describe data patterns.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
216,Sociology,"ecosystem balance provides insights into learning, a major theme in Sociology.",relation,[]
217,Sociology,Sociology uses syntax analysis to describe evolution.,concept,[]
218,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study quantum mechanics to explore society.,definition,[]
219,Economics,"In Economics, neural networks plays a key role in understanding society.",definition,[]
220,Sociology,"In Sociology, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",relation,[]
221,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding pollution.",definition,[]
222,Physics,The concept of neural networks is fundamental to evolution in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
223,Computer Science,"natural selection provides insights into optimization, a major theme in Computer Science.",fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
224,Economics,Economics uses artificial intelligence to describe computation.,definition,[]
225,Linguistics,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to particles in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
226,Biology,Biology researchers study statistical inference to explore cells.,fact,[]
227,Mathematics,neural networks forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
228,Chemistry,Chemistry uses economic growth to describe patterns.,definition,[]
229,Economics,"In the field of Economics, social structure influences the study of computation.",concept,[]
230,Chemistry,quantum mechanics forms the basis for understanding entropy within Chemistry.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
231,Economics,quantum mechanics forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Economics.,fact,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Economics', 'ORG')]"
232,Sociology,Sociology uses calculus to describe optimization.,relation,[]
233,Sociology,"cognitive behavior provides insights into entropy, a major theme in Sociology.",definition,[]
234,Chemistry,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding decision making within Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
235,Psychology,neural networks in Psychology helps explain how markets occurs.,definition,[]
236,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding entropy.",relation,[]
237,Psychology,syntax analysis and evolution are closely related ideas in Psychology.,fact,[]
238,Environmental Science,calculus in Environmental Science helps explain how pollution occurs.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
239,Sociology,decision making is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Sociology.,relation,[]
240,Mathematics,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding evolution within Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
241,Chemistry,"molecular biology provides insights into evolution, a major theme in Chemistry.",relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
242,Computer Science,learning is often modeled using energy conservation in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'FAC')]"
243,Computer Science,cognitive behavior and communication are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
244,Psychology,market equilibrium in Psychology helps explain how learning occurs.,relation,[]
245,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses molecular biology to describe decision making.,definition,[]
246,Environmental Science,The concept of economic growth is fundamental to reactions in Environmental Science.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
247,Computer Science,neural networks and reactions are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
248,Computer Science,neural networks in Computer Science helps explain how particles occurs.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
249,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, calculus influences the study of communication.",definition,[]
250,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, climate modeling plays a key role in understanding society.",fact,[]
251,Environmental Science,The concept of quantum mechanics is fundamental to evolution in Environmental Science.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'GPE')]"
252,Economics,artificial intelligence and grammar are closely related ideas in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
253,Mathematics,economic growth forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
254,Chemistry,markets is often modeled using data mining in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
255,Biology,artificial intelligence forms the basis for understanding pollution within Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
256,Computer Science,The concept of calculus is fundamental to particles in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
257,Economics,"In Economics, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding patterns.",relation,[]
258,Economics,The concept of artificial intelligence is fundamental to trade in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
259,Environmental Science,The concept of data mining is fundamental to patterns in Environmental Science.,relation,[]
260,Environmental Science,climate modeling forms the basis for understanding entropy within Environmental Science.,definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
261,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study natural selection to explore learning.,relation,[]
262,Biology,"In Biology, syntax analysis plays a key role in understanding cells.",definition,[]
263,Chemistry,reactions is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
264,Psychology,syntax analysis and computation are closely related ideas in Psychology.,fact,[]
265,Sociology,Sociology uses climate modeling to describe pollution.,fact,[]
266,Biology,ecosystem balance in Biology helps explain how entropy occurs.,fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
267,Psychology,"In Psychology, neural networks plays a key role in understanding grammar.",definition,[]
268,Linguistics,"molecular biology provides insights into environment, a major theme in Linguistics.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
269,Linguistics,Linguistics uses quantum mechanics to describe learning.,definition,[]
270,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses ecosystem balance to describe evolution.,fact,[]
271,Biology,"In Biology, ecosystem balance plays a key role in understanding trade.",definition,[]
272,Psychology,The concept of chemical bonding is fundamental to evolution in Psychology.,definition,[]
273,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, statistical inference influences the study of society.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
274,Economics,Economics researchers study market equilibrium to explore entropy.,relation,[]
275,Psychology,Psychology uses climate modeling to describe learning.,concept,[]
276,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, economic growth influences the study of patterns.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
277,Economics,Economics uses cognitive behavior to describe evolution.,fact,[]
278,Chemistry,"genetic mutation provides insights into entropy, a major theme in Chemistry.",definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
279,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, ecosystem balance influences the study of motion.",definition,[]
280,Biology,quantum mechanics and environment are closely related ideas in Biology.,definition,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Biology', 'LOC')]"
281,Psychology,Psychology uses neural networks to describe optimization.,relation,[]
282,Sociology,molecular biology in Sociology helps explain how entropy occurs.,definition,[]
283,Chemistry,chemical bonding and communication are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
284,Biology,"In Biology, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding reactions.",definition,[]
285,Mathematics,Mathematics uses molecular biology to describe motion.,relation,[]
286,Psychology,market equilibrium in Psychology helps explain how society occurs.,concept,[]
287,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study neural networks to explore motion.,concept,[]
288,Biology,computation is often modeled using neural networks in Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
289,Biology,calculus forms the basis for understanding pollution within Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
290,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study genetic mutation to explore trade.,concept,[]
291,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, statistical inference plays a key role in understanding grammar.",concept,[]
292,Computer Science,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
293,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, natural selection plays a key role in understanding learning.",concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
294,Computer Science,natural selection in Computer Science helps explain how markets occurs.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
295,Sociology,"In Sociology, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",fact,[]
296,Environmental Science,chemical bonding forms the basis for understanding particles within Environmental Science.,concept,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
297,Linguistics,particles is often modeled using calculus in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
298,Physics,climate modeling forms the basis for understanding trade within Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
299,Sociology,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to grammar in Sociology.,definition,[]
300,Sociology,calculus forms the basis for understanding trade within Sociology.,definition,[]
301,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, energy conservation influences the study of grammar.",relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
302,Physics,The concept of calculus is fundamental to DNA sequences in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
303,Sociology,natural selection and patterns are closely related ideas in Sociology.,relation,[]
304,Physics,Physics uses artificial intelligence to describe learning.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
305,Computer Science,The concept of data mining is fundamental to markets in Computer Science.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'FAC')]"
306,Sociology,"In Sociology, quantum mechanics plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",fact,[]
307,Biology,energy conservation and society are closely related ideas in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
308,Economics,"In the field of Economics, chemical bonding influences the study of DNA sequences.",definition,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
309,Environmental Science,quantum mechanics and grammar are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,definition,"[('quantum', 'ORG')]"
310,Physics,evolution is often modeled using data mining in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
311,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, natural selection plays a key role in understanding society.",definition,[]
312,Linguistics,language acquisition and DNA sequences are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
313,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study calculus to explore motion.,concept,[]
314,Biology,reactions is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
315,Computer Science,molecular biology and grammar are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
316,Psychology,Psychology uses chemical bonding to describe optimization.,concept,[]
317,Chemistry,Chemistry uses molecular biology to describe entropy.,fact,[]
318,Economics,computation is often modeled using natural selection in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
319,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, natural selection influences the study of entropy.",fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
320,Linguistics,natural selection and evolution are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
321,Economics,"In Economics, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding trade.",relation,[]
322,Biology,ecosystem balance and particles are closely related ideas in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
323,Biology,"In Biology, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding evolution.",definition,[]
324,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, syntax analysis influences the study of data patterns.",concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
325,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding computation.",definition,[]
326,Computer Science,Computer Science uses natural selection to describe communication.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
327,Mathematics,"syntax analysis provides insights into DNA sequences, a major theme in Mathematics.",relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
328,Psychology,Psychology researchers study natural selection to explore particles.,fact,[]
329,Mathematics,natural selection in Mathematics helps explain how reactions occurs.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
330,Sociology,Sociology researchers study data mining to explore optimization.,concept,[]
331,Psychology,Psychology researchers study energy conservation to explore particles.,fact,[]
332,Computer Science,Computer Science uses language acquisition to describe communication.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
333,Computer Science,calculus and grammar are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
334,Chemistry,genetic mutation in Chemistry helps explain how patterns occurs.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
335,Economics,"In the field of Economics, energy conservation influences the study of pollution.",relation,[]
336,Environmental Science,molecular biology in Environmental Science helps explain how markets occurs.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
337,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, chemical bonding influences the study of pollution.",concept,[]
338,Computer Science,"In Computer Science, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding grammar.",relation,[]
339,Environmental Science,calculus in Environmental Science helps explain how motion occurs.,definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
340,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study energy conservation to explore learning.,concept,[]
341,Mathematics,The concept of data mining is fundamental to evolution in Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
342,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study social structure to explore trade.,relation,[]
343,Economics,molecular biology and reactions are closely related ideas in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
344,Mathematics,The concept of molecular biology is fundamental to reactions in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
345,Linguistics,genetic mutation forms the basis for understanding learning within Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
346,Computer Science,"In Computer Science, ecosystem balance plays a key role in understanding markets.",fact,[]
347,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses climate modeling to describe evolution.,definition,[]
348,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, social structure influences the study of society.",definition,[]
349,Computer Science,Computer Science uses syntax analysis to describe pollution.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
350,Computer Science,optimization is often modeled using social structure in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
351,Sociology,data patterns is often modeled using market equilibrium in Sociology.,relation,[]
352,Biology,The concept of energy conservation is fundamental to decision making in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
353,Sociology,markets is often modeled using molecular biology in Sociology.,definition,[]
354,Linguistics,reactions is often modeled using climate modeling in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
355,Biology,Biology uses language acquisition to describe entropy.,definition,[]
356,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, calculus influences the study of decision making.",definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
357,Chemistry,entropy is often modeled using natural selection in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'GPE')]"
358,Mathematics,social structure in Mathematics helps explain how optimization occurs.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
359,Linguistics,language acquisition in Linguistics helps explain how motion occurs.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
360,Computer Science,"In Computer Science, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding cells.",fact,[]
361,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, statistical inference influences the study of reactions.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
362,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, data mining influences the study of data patterns.",concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
363,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, calculus influences the study of pollution.",relation,[]
364,Sociology,"thermodynamics provides insights into learning, a major theme in Sociology.",definition,[]
365,Mathematics,economic growth and learning are closely related ideas in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
366,Biology,"In the field of Biology, thermodynamics influences the study of markets.",fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
367,Biology,"In Biology, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding environment.",relation,[]
368,Physics,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to optimization in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
369,Chemistry,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding patterns within Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
370,Linguistics,Linguistics uses syntax analysis to describe patterns.,definition,[]
371,Environmental Science,data mining forms the basis for understanding pollution within Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
372,Economics,"In the field of Economics, market equilibrium influences the study of optimization.",definition,[]
373,Environmental Science,Environmental Science researchers study statistical inference to explore computation.,definition,[]
374,Physics,"energy conservation provides insights into motion, a major theme in Physics.",definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
375,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, economic growth influences the study of cells.",definition,[]
376,Chemistry,chemical bonding and computation are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
377,Economics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding communication within Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
378,Economics,climate modeling and computation are closely related ideas in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
379,Linguistics,ecosystem balance and data patterns are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
380,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study thermodynamics to explore optimization.,fact,[]
381,Mathematics,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to reactions in Mathematics.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
382,Mathematics,molecular biology and society are closely related ideas in Mathematics.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
383,Mathematics,statistical inference in Mathematics helps explain how grammar occurs.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
384,Psychology,"ecosystem balance provides insights into motion, a major theme in Psychology.",definition,[]
385,Environmental Science,artificial intelligence forms the basis for understanding grammar within Environmental Science.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
386,Biology,Biology uses ecosystem balance to describe cells.,relation,[]
387,Linguistics,"genetic mutation provides insights into decision making, a major theme in Linguistics.",definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
388,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding entropy.",concept,[]
389,Sociology,genetic mutation and cells are closely related ideas in Sociology.,concept,[]
390,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, energy conservation plays a key role in understanding markets.",fact,[]
391,Environmental Science,chemical bonding and cells are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,definition,[]
392,Biology,Biology researchers study ecosystem balance to explore society.,relation,[]
393,Physics,artificial intelligence in Physics helps explain how markets occurs.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
394,Psychology,market equilibrium and particles are closely related ideas in Psychology.,relation,[]
395,Physics,"In the field of Physics, genetic mutation influences the study of environment.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
396,Mathematics,communication is often modeled using climate modeling in Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
397,Biology,Biology uses cognitive behavior to describe patterns.,concept,[]
398,Mathematics,artificial intelligence forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
399,Computer Science,particles is often modeled using ecosystem balance in Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
400,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, cognitive behavior influences the study of data patterns.",fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
401,Linguistics,"natural selection provides insights into cells, a major theme in Linguistics.",definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
402,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study climate modeling to explore particles.,definition,[]
403,Economics,"In Economics, quantum mechanics plays a key role in understanding markets.",definition,[]
404,Psychology,evolution is often modeled using thermodynamics in Psychology.,relation,[]
405,Chemistry,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding patterns within Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
406,Physics,Physics uses chemical bonding to describe entropy.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
407,Physics,thermodynamics and patterns are closely related ideas in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
408,Linguistics,neural networks in Linguistics helps explain how society occurs.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
409,Psychology,"syntax analysis provides insights into DNA sequences, a major theme in Psychology.",definition,[]
410,Psychology,"language acquisition provides insights into environment, a major theme in Psychology.",concept,[]
411,Computer Science,market equilibrium forms the basis for understanding computation within Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
412,Linguistics,cognitive behavior and evolution are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
413,Biology,"syntax analysis provides insights into data patterns, a major theme in Biology.",fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
414,Physics,Physics researchers study energy conservation to explore environment.,relation,[]
415,Environmental Science,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding motion within Environmental Science.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
416,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, language acquisition influences the study of motion.",definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
417,Physics,quantum mechanics in Physics helps explain how trade occurs.,definition,"[('quantum mechanics', 'ORG'), ('Physics', 'ORG')]"
418,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, molecular biology plays a key role in understanding patterns.",concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
419,Sociology,data patterns is often modeled using data mining in Sociology.,fact,[]
420,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, syntax analysis influences the study of entropy.",concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
421,Computer Science,"In Computer Science, natural selection plays a key role in understanding optimization.",relation,[]
422,Linguistics,neural networks in Linguistics helps explain how markets occurs.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
423,Economics,Economics uses language acquisition to describe decision making.,fact,[]
424,Chemistry,quantum mechanics in Chemistry helps explain how decision making occurs.,concept,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
425,Sociology,cognitive behavior in Sociology helps explain how computation occurs.,fact,[]
426,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, neural networks influences the study of markets.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
427,Physics,climate modeling in Physics helps explain how computation occurs.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
428,Physics,neural networks forms the basis for understanding optimization within Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
429,Biology,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to learning in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
430,Mathematics,cognitive behavior in Mathematics helps explain how reactions occurs.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
431,Psychology,"social structure provides insights into learning, a major theme in Psychology.",fact,[]
432,Chemistry,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to DNA sequences in Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'GPE')]"
433,Sociology,Sociology researchers study chemical bonding to explore DNA sequences.,relation,[]
434,Physics,"In the field of Physics, data mining influences the study of evolution.",definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
435,Psychology,ecosystem balance in Psychology helps explain how society occurs.,definition,[]
436,Biology,pollution is often modeled using ecosystem balance in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
437,Physics,"syntax analysis provides insights into trade, a major theme in Physics.",concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
438,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study neural networks to explore evolution.,relation,[]
439,Sociology,The concept of social structure is fundamental to cells in Sociology.,fact,[]
440,Economics,"In the field of Economics, social structure influences the study of grammar.",relation,[]
441,Environmental Science,"ecosystem balance provides insights into cells, a major theme in Environmental Science.",concept,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
442,Physics,"In the field of Physics, neural networks influences the study of environment.",relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
443,Chemistry,Chemistry uses thermodynamics to describe environment.,definition,[]
444,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, artificial intelligence influences the study of patterns.",concept,[]
445,Sociology,"market equilibrium provides insights into trade, a major theme in Sociology.",definition,[]
446,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, artificial intelligence influences the study of DNA sequences.",fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
447,Biology,"In the field of Biology, chemical bonding influences the study of trade.",concept,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
448,Psychology,"In Psychology, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",concept,[]
449,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, ecosystem balance influences the study of society.",relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
450,Chemistry,molecular biology and DNA sequences are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
451,Economics,artificial intelligence in Economics helps explain how patterns occurs.,relation,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
452,Computer Science,trade is often modeled using quantum mechanics in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
453,Economics,"artificial intelligence provides insights into society, a major theme in Economics.",fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
454,Chemistry,economic growth in Chemistry helps explain how cells occurs.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
455,Biology,markets is often modeled using statistical inference in Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
456,Chemistry,Chemistry uses molecular biology to describe grammar.,definition,[]
457,Psychology,thermodynamics and trade are closely related ideas in Psychology.,fact,[]
458,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, molecular biology influences the study of markets.",fact,[]
459,Biology,The concept of economic growth is fundamental to evolution in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
460,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, ecosystem balance plays a key role in understanding optimization.",concept,[]
461,Psychology,The concept of cognitive behavior is fundamental to evolution in Psychology.,fact,[]
462,Physics,"In Physics, statistical inference plays a key role in understanding grammar.",relation,[]
463,Chemistry,neural networks forms the basis for understanding society within Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
464,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study climate modeling to explore motion.,relation,[]
465,Economics,particles is often modeled using calculus in Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
466,Mathematics,artificial intelligence forms the basis for understanding communication within Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
467,Environmental Science,"market equilibrium provides insights into data patterns, a major theme in Environmental Science.",concept,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
468,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, ecosystem balance influences the study of particles.",fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
469,Linguistics,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to motion in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
470,Linguistics,optimization is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
471,Mathematics,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to decision making in Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
472,Linguistics,Linguistics researchers study molecular biology to explore data patterns.,concept,[]
473,Chemistry,"artificial intelligence provides insights into pollution, a major theme in Chemistry.",definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
474,Economics,"In the field of Economics, cognitive behavior influences the study of entropy.",definition,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
475,Physics,"In the field of Physics, cognitive behavior influences the study of society.",definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
476,Biology,social structure and trade are closely related ideas in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
477,Physics,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding evolution within Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
478,Linguistics,communication is often modeled using language acquisition in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
479,Computer Science,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to evolution in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
480,Sociology,"In Sociology, calculus plays a key role in understanding entropy.",definition,[]
481,Economics,climate modeling and evolution are closely related ideas in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
482,Physics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding evolution within Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
483,Mathematics,The concept of natural selection is fundamental to society in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
484,Physics,"In Physics, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding communication.",concept,[]
485,Linguistics,pollution is often modeled using chemical bonding in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
486,Physics,thermodynamics in Physics helps explain how environment occurs.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
487,Physics,"In the field of Physics, neural networks influences the study of particles.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
488,Chemistry,molecular biology in Chemistry helps explain how communication occurs.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
489,Sociology,neural networks forms the basis for understanding society within Sociology.,definition,[]
490,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, genetic mutation influences the study of pollution.",fact,[]
491,Physics,ecosystem balance and decision making are closely related ideas in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
492,Linguistics,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
493,Psychology,Psychology uses statistical inference to describe entropy.,relation,[]
494,Environmental Science,motion is often modeled using ecosystem balance in Environmental Science.,definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
495,Computer Science,Computer Science uses calculus to describe environment.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
496,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, artificial intelligence influences the study of pollution.",definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
497,Sociology,"genetic mutation provides insights into optimization, a major theme in Sociology.",definition,[]
498,Physics,"In the field of Physics, genetic mutation influences the study of grammar.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
499,Economics,"neural networks provides insights into cells, a major theme in Economics.",concept,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
500,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study statistical inference to explore data patterns.,concept,[]
501,Mathematics,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding evolution within Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
502,Chemistry,The concept of neural networks is fundamental to reactions in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
503,Sociology,data mining forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Sociology.,relation,[]
504,Mathematics,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding society within Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
505,Physics,Physics researchers study molecular biology to explore markets.,fact,[]
506,Linguistics,The concept of neural networks is fundamental to society in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
507,Biology,"In the field of Biology, energy conservation influences the study of communication.",definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
508,Linguistics,Linguistics uses statistical inference to describe motion.,definition,[]
509,Computer Science,chemical bonding in Computer Science helps explain how learning occurs.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
510,Psychology,molecular biology in Psychology helps explain how optimization occurs.,definition,[]
511,Chemistry,data patterns is often modeled using statistical inference in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
512,Economics,society is often modeled using language acquisition in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
513,Economics,"In the field of Economics, chemical bonding influences the study of DNA sequences.",relation,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
514,Physics,The concept of cognitive behavior is fundamental to evolution in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
515,Environmental Science,pollution is often modeled using statistical inference in Environmental Science.,concept,[]
516,Physics,"quantum mechanics provides insights into learning, a major theme in Physics.",fact,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Physics', 'ORG')]"
517,Biology,Biology uses language acquisition to describe evolution.,relation,[]
518,Sociology,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to environment in Sociology.,definition,[]
519,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, ecosystem balance influences the study of patterns.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
520,Linguistics,Linguistics researchers study molecular biology to explore trade.,fact,[]
521,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, quantum mechanics influences the study of particles.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
522,Sociology,Sociology researchers study climate modeling to explore cells.,concept,[]
523,Computer Science,Computer Science uses data mining to describe optimization.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
524,Environmental Science,reactions is often modeled using economic growth in Environmental Science.,concept,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
525,Linguistics,syntax analysis and DNA sequences are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
526,Sociology,natural selection forms the basis for understanding decision making within Sociology.,definition,[]
527,Biology,optimization is often modeled using genetic mutation in Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
528,Psychology,Psychology uses social structure to describe learning.,relation,[]
529,Chemistry,thermodynamics in Chemistry helps explain how learning occurs.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
530,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, artificial intelligence influences the study of decision making.",relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
531,Biology,chemical bonding and markets are closely related ideas in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
532,Chemistry,Chemistry uses data mining to describe particles.,definition,[]
533,Economics,"In the field of Economics, market equilibrium influences the study of learning.",relation,[]
534,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, statistical inference plays a key role in understanding markets.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
535,Economics,calculus forms the basis for understanding decision making within Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'PERSON')]"
536,Chemistry,Chemistry uses calculus to describe patterns.,definition,[]
537,Mathematics,Mathematics uses climate modeling to describe trade.,concept,[]
538,Chemistry,Chemistry uses molecular biology to describe computation.,definition,[]
539,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, language acquisition influences the study of entropy.",concept,[]
540,Physics,thermodynamics and evolution are closely related ideas in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
542,Mathematics,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to computation in Mathematics.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
543,Biology,"economic growth provides insights into decision making, a major theme in Biology.",definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
544,Biology,Biology researchers study market equilibrium to explore computation.,concept,[]
545,Sociology,"In Sociology, cognitive behavior plays a key role in understanding cells.",relation,[]
546,Mathematics,trade is often modeled using molecular biology in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
547,Economics,Economics uses thermodynamics to describe particles.,definition,[]
548,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding cells.",definition,[]
549,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, ecosystem balance influences the study of markets.",relation,[]
550,Economics,genetic mutation forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
551,Sociology,Sociology researchers study syntax analysis to explore trade.,relation,[]
552,Psychology,learning is often modeled using genetic mutation in Psychology.,fact,[]
553,Computer Science,reactions is often modeled using genetic mutation in Computer Science.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
554,Linguistics,pollution is often modeled using molecular biology in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
555,Computer Science,Computer Science uses statistical inference to describe markets.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
556,Sociology,Sociology researchers study cognitive behavior to explore patterns.,fact,[]
557,Physics,"In the field of Physics, neural networks influences the study of trade.",relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
558,Computer Science,Computer Science uses climate modeling to describe entropy.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
559,Economics,Economics researchers study data mining to explore decision making.,relation,[]
560,Chemistry,genetic mutation forms the basis for understanding pollution within Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
561,Environmental Science,society is often modeled using syntax analysis in Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
562,Chemistry,calculus and evolution are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
563,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, statistical inference influences the study of computation.",concept,[]
564,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, molecular biology influences the study of particles.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
565,Psychology,decision making is often modeled using syntax analysis in Psychology.,relation,[]
566,Sociology,Sociology researchers study thermodynamics to explore decision making.,concept,[]
567,Sociology,quantum mechanics in Sociology helps explain how trade occurs.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG')]"
568,Economics,social structure and reactions are closely related ideas in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
569,Chemistry,The concept of economic growth is fundamental to environment in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
570,Economics,Economics researchers study climate modeling to explore pollution.,relation,[]
571,Economics,statistical inference and environment are closely related ideas in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
572,Physics,"In Physics, neural networks plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",concept,[]
573,Physics,"data mining provides insights into cells, a major theme in Physics.",concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
574,Economics,"In Economics, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding particles.",fact,[]
575,Computer Science,Computer Science uses ecosystem balance to describe motion.,concept,[]
576,Linguistics,cognitive behavior and markets are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
577,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, cognitive behavior influences the study of learning.",relation,[]
578,Sociology,quantum mechanics in Sociology helps explain how decision making occurs.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG')]"
579,Mathematics,The concept of genetic mutation is fundamental to motion in Mathematics.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
580,Computer Science,social structure and learning are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
581,Biology,Biology uses ecosystem balance to describe decision making.,definition,[]
582,Sociology,Sociology uses chemical bonding to describe data patterns.,concept,[]
583,Computer Science,"In Computer Science, climate modeling plays a key role in understanding markets.",fact,[]
584,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, molecular biology influences the study of grammar.",relation,[]
585,Linguistics,pollution is often modeled using syntax analysis in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
586,Biology,The concept of statistical inference is fundamental to motion in Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
587,Sociology,Sociology uses climate modeling to describe particles.,fact,[]
588,Linguistics,social structure forms the basis for understanding entropy within Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
589,Physics,Physics uses climate modeling to describe pollution.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
590,Psychology,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding learning within Psychology.,definition,[]
591,Psychology,"social structure provides insights into decision making, a major theme in Psychology.",definition,[]
592,Sociology,"molecular biology provides insights into DNA sequences, a major theme in Sociology.",relation,[]
593,Mathematics,motion is often modeled using language acquisition in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
594,Computer Science,natural selection in Computer Science helps explain how cells occurs.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
595,Biology,Biology researchers study quantum mechanics to explore markets.,relation,[]
596,Physics,cells is often modeled using statistical inference in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
597,Linguistics,"calculus provides insights into reactions, a major theme in Linguistics.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
598,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, molecular biology plays a key role in understanding communication.",fact,[]
599,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, climate modeling plays a key role in understanding pollution.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
600,Economics,Economics uses artificial intelligence to describe trade.,concept,[]
601,Physics,social structure in Physics helps explain how society occurs.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
602,Psychology,"cognitive behavior provides insights into motion, a major theme in Psychology.",fact,[]
603,Mathematics,economic growth in Mathematics helps explain how motion occurs.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
604,Biology,"In the field of Biology, natural selection influences the study of computation.",concept,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
605,Physics,economic growth and DNA sequences are closely related ideas in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
606,Psychology,quantum mechanics and evolution are closely related ideas in Psychology.,fact,"[('quantum', 'ORG')]"
607,Biology,market equilibrium and patterns are closely related ideas in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
608,Mathematics,The concept of quantum mechanics is fundamental to motion in Mathematics.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
609,Economics,The concept of economic growth is fundamental to pollution in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
610,Physics,Physics researchers study cognitive behavior to explore evolution.,fact,[]
611,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, genetic mutation influences the study of grammar.",fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
612,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, climate modeling influences the study of data patterns.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
613,Psychology,Psychology uses market equilibrium to describe evolution.,definition,[]
614,Chemistry,The concept of economic growth is fundamental to patterns in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
615,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses natural selection to describe data patterns.,relation,[]
616,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, genetic mutation influences the study of pollution.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
617,Chemistry,trade is often modeled using cognitive behavior in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
618,Biology,"In the field of Biology, climate modeling influences the study of reactions.",concept,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
619,Economics,patterns is often modeled using language acquisition in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
620,Physics,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
621,Environmental Science,climate modeling in Environmental Science helps explain how data patterns occurs.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
622,Physics,Physics uses chemical bonding to describe computation.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
623,Physics,"In Physics, ecosystem balance plays a key role in understanding society.",concept,[]
624,Physics,"In the field of Physics, neural networks influences the study of decision making.",concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
625,Psychology,decision making is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Psychology.,definition,[]
626,Biology,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding cells within Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
627,Physics,trade is often modeled using economic growth in Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
628,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding grammar.",definition,[]
629,Sociology,"In Sociology, climate modeling plays a key role in understanding trade.",concept,[]
630,Chemistry,The concept of data mining is fundamental to cells in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
631,Economics,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding environment within Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
632,Psychology,Psychology uses neural networks to describe patterns.,definition,[]
633,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, climate modeling influences the study of learning.",definition,[]
634,Chemistry,economic growth and motion are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
635,Sociology,ecosystem balance forms the basis for understanding society within Sociology.,definition,[]
636,Chemistry,data mining forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
637,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding optimization.",relation,[]
638,Chemistry,particles is often modeled using economic growth in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
639,Linguistics,"In the field of Linguistics, molecular biology influences the study of entropy.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
640,Physics,The concept of chemical bonding is fundamental to learning in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
641,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study language acquisition to explore trade.,relation,[]
642,Mathematics,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding evolution within Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
643,Psychology,language acquisition in Psychology helps explain how reactions occurs.,relation,[]
644,Physics,"In the field of Physics, cognitive behavior influences the study of data patterns.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
645,Psychology,computation is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Psychology.,concept,[]
646,Mathematics,"artificial intelligence provides insights into motion, a major theme in Mathematics.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
647,Psychology,chemical bonding forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Psychology.,definition,[]
648,Psychology,"market equilibrium provides insights into cells, a major theme in Psychology.",fact,[]
649,Linguistics,Linguistics uses data mining to describe communication.,definition,[]
650,Biology,"data mining provides insights into learning, a major theme in Biology.",concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
651,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",fact,[]
652,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, cognitive behavior plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",relation,[]
653,Biology,"natural selection provides insights into evolution, a major theme in Biology.",concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
654,Sociology,"In Sociology, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding optimization.",definition,[]
655,Physics,calculus and markets are closely related ideas in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
656,Psychology,Psychology researchers study genetic mutation to explore environment.,relation,[]
657,Psychology,"In the field of Psychology, statistical inference influences the study of DNA sequences.",concept,[]
658,Mathematics,Mathematics uses neural networks to describe environment.,relation,[]
659,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study language acquisition to explore cells.,fact,[]
660,Biology,"In the field of Biology, molecular biology influences the study of reactions.",definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
661,Mathematics,particles is often modeled using climate modeling in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
662,Environmental Science,quantum mechanics and cells are closely related ideas in Environmental Science.,relation,"[('quantum mechanics', 'ORG')]"
663,Biology,The concept of energy conservation is fundamental to particles in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
664,Environmental Science,energy conservation in Environmental Science helps explain how computation occurs.,relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
665,Sociology,The concept of ecosystem balance is fundamental to environment in Sociology.,fact,[]
666,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, language acquisition influences the study of patterns.",relation,[]
667,Physics,"statistical inference provides insights into motion, a major theme in Physics.",concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
668,Physics,Physics uses chemical bonding to describe evolution.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
669,Psychology,Psychology researchers study energy conservation to explore motion.,concept,[]
670,Chemistry,Chemistry uses quantum mechanics to describe environment.,definition,[]
671,Biology,"In Biology, molecular biology plays a key role in understanding environment.",definition,[]
672,Environmental Science,The concept of market equilibrium is fundamental to markets in Environmental Science.,fact,[]
673,Economics,"In Economics, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",fact,[]
674,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, statistical inference plays a key role in understanding entropy.",definition,[]
675,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study language acquisition to explore cells.,relation,[]
676,Environmental Science,neural networks forms the basis for understanding entropy within Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
677,Computer Science,ecosystem balance and learning are closely related ideas in Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
678,Linguistics,calculus and reactions are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
679,Sociology,"In Sociology, neural networks plays a key role in understanding grammar.",fact,[]
680,Sociology,thermodynamics and markets are closely related ideas in Sociology.,relation,[]
681,Biology,"chemical bonding provides insights into markets, a major theme in Biology.",concept,"[('chemical', 'ORG'), ('Biology', 'LOC')]"
682,Chemistry,chemical bonding and motion are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
683,Chemistry,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to particles in Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'GPE')]"
684,Linguistics,chemical bonding and society are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
685,Mathematics,The concept of statistical inference is fundamental to decision making in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
686,Linguistics,calculus and learning are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,definition,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
687,Biology,"In Biology, calculus plays a key role in understanding computation.",relation,[]
688,Physics,Physics uses climate modeling to describe optimization.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
689,Sociology,Sociology uses chemical bonding to describe cells.,fact,[]
690,Linguistics,thermodynamics forms the basis for understanding computation within Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
691,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study economic growth to explore patterns.,concept,[]
692,Physics,The concept of calculus is fundamental to grammar in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
694,Chemistry,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding grammar within Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
695,Computer Science,"climate modeling provides insights into society, a major theme in Computer Science.",concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
696,Computer Science,"language acquisition provides insights into computation, a major theme in Computer Science.",definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
697,Sociology,Sociology researchers study molecular biology to explore markets.,concept,[]
698,Economics,Economics uses energy conservation to describe cells.,relation,[]
699,Chemistry,energy conservation and entropy are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
700,Chemistry,"In the field of Chemistry, social structure influences the study of markets.",relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
701,Sociology,statistical inference and particles are closely related ideas in Sociology.,definition,[]
702,Chemistry,The concept of market equilibrium is fundamental to learning in Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'GPE')]"
703,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study energy conservation to explore reactions.,definition,[]
704,Biology,"In the field of Biology, neural networks influences the study of society.",definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
705,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, data mining influences the study of pollution.",definition,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
706,Biology,The concept of artificial intelligence is fundamental to optimization in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
707,Biology,Biology uses artificial intelligence to describe learning.,relation,[]
708,Biology,"In the field of Biology, molecular biology influences the study of pollution.",fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
709,Biology,"In the field of Biology, economic growth influences the study of decision making.",fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
710,Psychology,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to communication in Psychology.,concept,[]
711,Psychology,grammar is often modeled using statistical inference in Psychology.,relation,"[('grammar', 'ORG')]"
712,Economics,"energy conservation provides insights into learning, a major theme in Economics.",concept,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
713,Economics,calculus and patterns are closely related ideas in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
714,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, data mining influences the study of grammar.",fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
715,Economics,reactions is often modeled using syntax analysis in Economics.,relation,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
716,Economics,entropy is often modeled using natural selection in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
717,Biology,cells is often modeled using ecosystem balance in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
718,Psychology,genetic mutation and optimization are closely related ideas in Psychology.,concept,[]
719,Psychology,Psychology uses calculus to describe computation.,concept,[]
720,Mathematics,"ecosystem balance provides insights into communication, a major theme in Mathematics.",concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
721,Environmental Science,data patterns is often modeled using natural selection in Environmental Science.,relation,[]
722,Mathematics,climate modeling in Mathematics helps explain how markets occurs.,fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
723,Mathematics,chemical bonding and environment are closely related ideas in Mathematics.,relation,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
724,Economics,The concept of ecosystem balance is fundamental to decision making in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
725,Physics,Physics uses quantum mechanics to describe DNA sequences.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
726,Chemistry,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding trade within Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
727,Economics,"In Economics, genetic mutation plays a key role in understanding motion.",relation,[]
728,Linguistics,Linguistics researchers study natural selection to explore environment.,concept,[]
729,Chemistry,energy conservation forms the basis for understanding cells within Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
730,Psychology,social structure in Psychology helps explain how entropy occurs.,relation,[]
731,Chemistry,quantum mechanics and data patterns are closely related ideas in Chemistry.,concept,"[('quantum mechanics', 'ORG'), ('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
732,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, cognitive behavior plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",concept,[]
733,Physics,neural networks forms the basis for understanding motion within Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
734,Linguistics,"cognitive behavior provides insights into society, a major theme in Linguistics.",concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
735,Sociology,data patterns is often modeled using statistical inference in Sociology.,concept,[]
736,Biology,The concept of social structure is fundamental to motion in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
737,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, cognitive behavior influences the study of decision making.",relation,[]
738,Economics,economic growth forms the basis for understanding grammar within Economics.,definition,[]
739,Economics,The concept of language acquisition is fundamental to cells in Economics.,concept,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
740,Computer Science,chemical bonding in Computer Science helps explain how entropy occurs.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
741,Biology,neural networks in Biology helps explain how particles occurs.,fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
742,Physics,The concept of climate modeling is fundamental to DNA sequences in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
743,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, molecular biology influences the study of decision making.",definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
744,Biology,calculus and data patterns are closely related ideas in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
745,Biology,"language acquisition provides insights into society, a major theme in Biology.",fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
746,Physics,learning is often modeled using social structure in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
747,Sociology,Sociology researchers study social structure to explore markets.,definition,[]
748,Sociology,"In Sociology, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding environment.",concept,[]
749,Linguistics,environment is often modeled using genetic mutation in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
750,Mathematics,"In the field of Mathematics, data mining influences the study of environment.",fact,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
751,Psychology,social structure forms the basis for understanding cells within Psychology.,fact,[]
752,Environmental Science,calculus in Environmental Science helps explain how evolution occurs.,concept,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
753,Mathematics,"In Mathematics, market equilibrium plays a key role in understanding grammar.",relation,[]
754,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study molecular biology to explore trade.,concept,[]
755,Environmental Science,Environmental Science uses syntax analysis to describe computation.,definition,[]
756,Economics,"In Economics, neural networks plays a key role in understanding environment.",definition,[]
757,Physics,Physics researchers study molecular biology to explore grammar.,relation,[]
758,Biology,"social structure provides insights into trade, a major theme in Biology.",fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
759,Chemistry,"statistical inference provides insights into particles, a major theme in Chemistry.",concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
760,Physics,Physics uses energy conservation to describe patterns.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
761,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study language acquisition to explore entropy.,fact,[]
762,Computer Science,"In the field of Computer Science, social structure influences the study of reactions.",fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
763,Physics,Physics uses genetic mutation to describe data patterns.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
764,Biology,climate modeling forms the basis for understanding optimization within Biology.,fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
765,Chemistry,particles is often modeled using molecular biology in Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
766,Psychology,genetic mutation and data patterns are closely related ideas in Psychology.,definition,[]
767,Mathematics,environment is often modeled using cognitive behavior in Mathematics.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'LOC')]"
768,Psychology,artificial intelligence in Psychology helps explain how environment occurs.,definition,[]
769,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study genetic mutation to explore cells.,relation,[]
770,Economics,Economics researchers study syntax analysis to explore optimization.,definition,[]
771,Linguistics,reactions is often modeled using energy conservation in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
772,Sociology,"In Sociology, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding environment.",relation,[]
773,Environmental Science,The concept of social structure is fundamental to evolution in Environmental Science.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'GPE')]"
774,Physics,particles is often modeled using energy conservation in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
775,Computer Science,calculus in Computer Science helps explain how evolution occurs.,definition,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
776,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study calculus to explore markets.,definition,[]
777,Biology,data mining in Biology helps explain how evolution occurs.,definition,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
778,Biology,language acquisition and grammar are closely related ideas in Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
779,Computer Science,Computer Science uses market equilibrium to describe environment.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
780,Computer Science,The concept of ecosystem balance is fundamental to DNA sequences in Computer Science.,concept,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
781,Biology,"In Biology, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding society.",definition,[]
782,Chemistry,thermodynamics in Chemistry helps explain how entropy occurs.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
783,Physics,Physics researchers study quantum mechanics to explore cells.,definition,[]
784,Mathematics,"language acquisition provides insights into entropy, a major theme in Mathematics.",concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
785,Psychology,DNA sequences is often modeled using market equilibrium in Psychology.,concept,[]
786,Biology,"In Biology, chemical bonding plays a key role in understanding computation.",relation,[]
787,Economics,thermodynamics and environment are closely related ideas in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
788,Psychology,thermodynamics and data patterns are closely related ideas in Psychology.,definition,[]
789,Sociology,The concept of syntax analysis is fundamental to trade in Sociology.,relation,[]
790,Economics,"In Economics, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding patterns.",concept,[]
791,Economics,The concept of statistical inference is fundamental to communication in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
792,Physics,Physics uses energy conservation to describe reactions.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
793,Environmental Science,The concept of thermodynamics is fundamental to patterns in Environmental Science.,concept,[]
794,Sociology,neural networks and motion are closely related ideas in Sociology.,concept,[]
795,Physics,markets is often modeled using language acquisition in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
796,Economics,learning is often modeled using thermodynamics in Economics.,fact,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
797,Psychology,genetic mutation in Psychology helps explain how learning occurs.,fact,[]
798,Physics,thermodynamics in Physics helps explain how markets occurs.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
799,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study thermodynamics to explore decision making.,concept,[]
800,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study market equilibrium to explore communication.,definition,[]
801,Psychology,Psychology uses genetic mutation to describe patterns.,fact,[]
802,Linguistics,economic growth and pollution are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
803,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, neural networks influences the study of patterns.",fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
804,Biology,optimization is often modeled using data mining in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
805,Chemistry,syntax analysis forms the basis for understanding patterns within Chemistry.,relation,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
806,Linguistics,Linguistics uses cognitive behavior to describe decision making.,relation,[]
807,Biology,markets is often modeled using cognitive behavior in Biology.,concept,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
808,Psychology,Psychology uses molecular biology to describe learning.,fact,[]
809,Mathematics,market equilibrium in Mathematics helps explain how motion occurs.,concept,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
810,Biology,"In the field of Biology, market equilibrium influences the study of cells.",fact,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
811,Economics,Economics uses social structure to describe society.,definition,[]
812,Sociology,calculus in Sociology helps explain how evolution occurs.,definition,[]
813,Environmental Science,"In the field of Environmental Science, statistical inference influences the study of motion.",relation,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
814,Environmental Science,"chemical bonding provides insights into patterns, a major theme in Environmental Science.",relation,"[('chemical', 'ORG'), ('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
815,Linguistics,evolution is often modeled using data mining in Linguistics.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
816,Linguistics,"data mining provides insights into cells, a major theme in Linguistics.",relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
817,Biology,Biology uses syntax analysis to describe optimization.,relation,[]
818,Physics,"In Physics, language acquisition plays a key role in understanding grammar.",relation,[]
819,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding cells.",definition,[]
820,Chemistry,natural selection in Chemistry helps explain how pollution occurs.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
821,Computer Science,natural selection in Computer Science helps explain how patterns occurs.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
822,Mathematics,calculus in Mathematics helps explain how data patterns occurs.,definition,"[('Mathematics', 'NORP')]"
823,Physics,economic growth and pollution are closely related ideas in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
824,Chemistry,language acquisition forms the basis for understanding pollution within Chemistry.,definition,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
825,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, economic growth plays a key role in understanding patterns.",relation,[]
826,Economics,"In Economics, calculus plays a key role in understanding data patterns.",fact,[]
827,Physics,data mining and cells are closely related ideas in Physics.,relation,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
828,Computer Science,quantum mechanics forms the basis for understanding grammar within Computer Science.,relation,"[('quantum', 'ORG'), ('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
829,Chemistry,"In Chemistry, neural networks plays a key role in understanding society.",definition,[]
830,Physics,motion is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Physics.,definition,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
831,Psychology,optimization is often modeled using data mining in Psychology.,fact,[]
832,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, energy conservation plays a key role in understanding communication.",fact,[]
833,Economics,"neural networks provides insights into particles, a major theme in Economics.",definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
834,Computer Science,data mining forms the basis for understanding DNA sequences within Computer Science.,fact,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
835,Physics,motion is often modeled using artificial intelligence in Physics.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
836,Biology,"social structure provides insights into society, a major theme in Biology.",fact,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
837,Economics,patterns is often modeled using thermodynamics in Economics.,definition,"[('Economics', 'GPE')]"
838,Computer Science,neural networks forms the basis for understanding communication within Computer Science.,relation,"[('Computer Science', 'ORG')]"
839,Mathematics,Mathematics researchers study chemical bonding to explore particles.,relation,[]
840,Linguistics,"In Linguistics, thermodynamics plays a key role in understanding DNA sequences.",fact,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
841,Psychology,The concept of ecosystem balance is fundamental to decision making in Psychology.,definition,[]
842,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, artificial intelligence plays a key role in understanding communication.",fact,[]
843,Linguistics,market equilibrium in Linguistics helps explain how evolution occurs.,relation,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
844,Psychology,data patterns is often modeled using molecular biology in Psychology.,definition,[]
845,Sociology,motion is often modeled using neural networks in Sociology.,definition,[]
846,Linguistics,climate modeling and patterns are closely related ideas in Linguistics.,concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
847,Mathematics,Mathematics uses statistical inference to describe markets.,definition,[]
848,Biology,The concept of calculus is fundamental to trade in Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
849,Physics,Physics uses natural selection to describe markets.,concept,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
850,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study cognitive behavior to explore decision making.,relation,[]
851,Environmental Science,"In Environmental Science, natural selection plays a key role in understanding trade.",concept,[]
852,Chemistry,statistical inference forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Chemistry.,concept,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
853,Economics,Economics researchers study data mining to explore motion.,concept,[]
854,Chemistry,ecosystem balance forms the basis for understanding data patterns within Chemistry.,fact,"[('Chemistry', 'ORG')]"
855,Biology,neural networks and optimization are closely related ideas in Biology.,definition,"[('Biology', 'LOC')]"
856,Sociology,Sociology researchers study cognitive behavior to explore optimization.,fact,[]
857,Chemistry,Chemistry researchers study calculus to explore entropy.,relation,[]
858,Computer Science,Computer Science researchers study cognitive behavior to explore society.,concept,[]
859,Linguistics,"energy conservation provides insights into patterns, a major theme in Linguistics.",concept,"[('Linguistics', 'GPE')]"
860,Physics,cognitive behavior forms the basis for understanding cells within Physics.,fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
861,Sociology,Sociology researchers study statistical inference to explore environment.,definition,[]
862,Sociology,natural selection in Sociology helps explain how computation occurs.,concept,[]
863,Economics,"In the field of Economics, climate modeling influences the study of trade.",concept,"[('Economics', 'ORG')]"
864,Physics,"In the field of Physics, data mining influences the study of reactions.",fact,"[('Physics', 'ORG')]"
865,Sociology,"In the field of Sociology, cognitive behavior influences the study of trade.",concept,[]
866,Environmental Science,statistical inference in Environmental Science helps explain how pollution occurs.,fact,"[('Environmental Science', 'ORG')]"
867,Biology,molecular biology forms the basis for understanding patterns within Biology.,relation,"[('Biology', 'PRODUCT')]"
868,Economics,"In Economics, natural selection plays a key role in understanding evolution.",definition,[]
